Lloyd E. Cotsen collection of Potter Family photographs,1865-1935: Finding Aid
Cotsen Children's Library
- Landscapes, 1880 May-1913 September; 1021 items
  - Windermere from Brockhole, 1911 September 26; 1103; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 26 1911 / Windermere from Brockhole / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1102.
  - Windermere from Brockhole, 1911 September 26; 1104; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 26 1911 / Windermere from Brockhole / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1105.
  - Windermere from Brockhole, 1911 September 26; 1105; 1 item 16.5 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 26 1911 / Windermere from Brockhole / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1104.
  - The Croft, Windermere, 1911 September 29; 1106; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 29 1911 / The Croft / Windermere / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1107; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1108; 1 item 16.6 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1109-1110.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1109; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1108, 1110.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1110; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1108-1109.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1111; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1112-1117.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1112; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111, 1113-1117.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1113; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111-1112, 1114-1117.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1114; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111-1113, 1115-1117.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1115; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111-1114, 1116-1117. Torn.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1116; 1 item 16.5 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111-1115, 1117, trimmed down.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, 1911 September; 1117; 1 item 16.5 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1111-1116, trimmed down.
  - Lindeth How grounds, 1911 October 1; 1118; 1 item 16.1 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Oct 1. 1911 / Lindeth How / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Lindeth How, garden and gate in foreground, 1911 September; 1119; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lindeth How stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1911 / Windermere from Lindeth How / R Potter.
  - Behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, early morning, 1912 April; 1120; 1 item 8.2 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Behind Ferry / Hotel / Early morning / R Potter.
    Catalog number: 469
  - Behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1121; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Behind / Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1122-1124
  - Behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1122; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere / Behind Ferry / Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1121, 1123-1124
  - Behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1123; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere / Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1121-1122, 1124.
  - Beached boat behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1124; 1 item 8.2 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Behind / Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1121-1123.
  - Dock and boat behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1125; 1 item 8.2 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1126.
  - Dock and boat behind Ferry Hotel, Windermere, 1912 April; 1126; 1 item 8.2 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1125.
  - Windermere behind Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1127; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1128.
  - Windermere behind Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1128; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1127.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1129; 1 item 8.2 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere from Ferry / Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1130.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1130; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere from Ferry / Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1129.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1131; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere from Ferry Hotel / o R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1132.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1132; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Ferry Hotel Windermere / o R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1131.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1133; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / o R Potter.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1134; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: April 1912 / Windermere / Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1135.
  - Windermere from Ferry Hotel, 1912 April; 1135; 1 item 12.0 x 16.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1912 / Windermere Ferry Hotel / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1134.
  - Windermere Ferry, 1912 May; 1136; 1 item 7.4 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: May 1912 / Windermere Ferry / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1137.
  - Windermere Ferry, 1912 May; 1137; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Windermere Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: May 1912 / Windermere Ferry / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1136.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1138; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1139. Torn.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1139; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1138. Torn.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1140; 1 item 16.4 x 21.8 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1141-1145.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1141; 1 item 16.4 x 21.8 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1140, 1142-1145. Torn.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1142; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1140-1141, 1143-1145.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1143; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1140-1142, 1144-1145.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1144; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1140-1143.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1145; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1146.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July 7; 1146; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 7 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1145.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1147; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1148.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1148; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1147.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1149; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1150; 1 item 16.5 x 21.7 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1151; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1152-1153.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1152; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1151, 1153.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1153; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1151-1152.
  - Sailboats on Windermere, from Broad Leys, 1912 July; 1154; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter.
  - Grasmere Church, children with flowers, 1912 August 3; 1155; 1 item 7.4 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 3 1912 / Grasmere Church / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August 12; 1156; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August 12; 1157; 1 item 16.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1158. Torn.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August 12; 1158; 1 item 16.5 x 21.7 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1157.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1159; 1 item 12.1 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1160-1163.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1160; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1159, 1161-1163.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1161; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1159-1160, 1162-1163.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1162; 1 item 12.1 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1159-1161, 1163.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1163; 1 item 12.1 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1159-1162.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1164; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1165-1169. Dated Aug 1912 in database because all other prints from same negative are thus dated.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1165; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1164, 1166-1169.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1166; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1164-1165 1166-1169.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1167; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1164-1166, 1168-1169.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1168; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1164-1167, 1169.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1169; 1 item 12.0 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1164-1168.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1170; 1 item 12.1 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1171; 1 item 12.1 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1172-1173.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1172; 1 item 12.1 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1171, 1173.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1173; 1 item 12.1 x 16.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1171-1172.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1174; 1 item 12.1 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1175.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1175; 1 item 12.1 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1174.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1176; 1 item 12.9 x 21.8 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1177-1180.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1177; 1 item 12.7 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1176, 1178-1180.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1178; 1 item 12.9 x 21.7 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1176-1177, 1179-1180.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1179; 1 item 12.6 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1176-1178, 1180.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1180; 1 item 13.0 x 21.7 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1176-1179.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1181; 1 item 21.6 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1182.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1182; 1 item 21.7 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1181.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1183; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1184; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1185.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1185; 1 item 15.5 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1184.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1186; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1187.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1187; 1 item 16.4 x 21.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1912 / Windermere from Broad Leys / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1186.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1912 August; 1188; 1 item 16.5 x 21.7 cm.